<resources>
    <string name="app_name">followalbase</string>
    <string-array name="WheelArrayDefault">
        <item>Off</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="read_more">show more</string>
    <string name="read_less">show less</string>

    <string name="Permissions_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="Permissions_not_now">Not now</string>
    <string name="Permissions_permission_required">Permission required</string>

    <string name="camera_permission">To capture photos and video, allow All-In-One Alarm access to the camera.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_permanently_denied">All-In-One Alarm needs the Camera permission to take photos or video, but it has been permanently denied. Please continue to app settings, select \"Permissions\", and enable \"Camera\".</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_denied">All-In-One Alarm needs Camera permissions to take photos or video</string>

    <string name="location_permission">To capture photos and video, allow All-In-One Alarm access to the camera.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_permanently_denied">All-In-One requires Location permission in order to get solar information, but it has been permanently denied. Please continue to the app settings menu, select \"Permissions\", and enable \"Location\".</string>
    <string name="location_permission_denied">All-In-One Alarm needs Location permissions to get solar information</string>
    <string name="contacts_permission_permanently_denied">All-In-One requires Contacts permission in order to get memory type alarm information, but it has been permanently denied. Please continue to the app settings menu, select \"Permissions\", and enable \"Contacts\".</string>
    <string name="contacts_permission_denied">All-In-One Alarm needs Contacts permissions to get memory type alarm information</string>


    <string name="ycuwq_datepicker_hour">H</string>
    <string name="ycuwq_datepicker_minute">m</string>


    <string name="time_ago_now">few moments ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_seconds">%1$d seconds ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_minute">%1$d minute ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_minutes">%1$d minutes ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_hour">%1$d hour ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_hours">%1$d hours ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_yesterday_at">Yesterday at %1$s</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_days">%1$d days ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_month">%1$d month ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_full_months">%1$d months ago</string>

    <string name="time_ago_seconds">%1$d sec ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_minute">%1$d min ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_minutes">%1$d min ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_hour">%1$d h ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_hours">%1$d h ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_yesterday_at">Yesterday at %1$s</string>
    <string name="time_ago_days">%1$d d ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_month">%1$d m ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_months">%1$d m ago</string>

    <string name="action_yes">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_no">No</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="title_permission_denied">Permission denied</string>
    <string name="btn_i_am_sure">I\'m sure</string>
    <string name="btn_retry">Re-Try</string>
    <string name="msg_sms_permission_denied">Without this permission the app is unable to detect verification code received in your SMS. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_otp_detection_disabled">SMS permission is not allowed. So auto detection of OTP is disabled.</string>
    <string name="msg_camera_picture_permission_denied">Without the camera and storage permissions the app is unable to open camera, take a picture and store to the device. Are you sure you want to deny these permissions?</string>
    <string name="msg_camera_picture_permission">To capture a picture and store to the device the application requires access to the camera and storage. Can you allow camera and storage permissions?</string>
    <string name="msg_camera_video_permission_denied">Without the camera and storage permissions the app is unable to open camera and take a video. Are you sure you want to deny these permissions?</string>
    <string name="msg_camera_video_permission">To take a video the application requires access to the camera and storage. Can you allow camera and storage permissions?</string>
    <string name="msg_location_permission_denied">Without the location permission the app is unable to open map and pick location. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_location_permission">To pick location the application requires location permission. Can you allow the permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_storage_permission_denied">Without the storage permission the app is unable to run perfectly. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_storage_permission">The application requires storage permission to run perfectly. Can you allow storage permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_gallery_permission_denied">Without the storage permission the app is unable to pick image from gallery. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_gallery_permission">To pick image from gallery the application requires storage permission. Can you allow storage permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_contacts_permission_denied">Without the contacts permission the app is unable to get contacts information. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_contacts_permission">The application requires contacts permission to get contacts information. Can you allow contacts permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_microphone_permission_denied">Without the microphone permission the app is unable to record audio. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_microphone_permission">The application requires microphone permission to record audio. Can you allow microphone permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_basic_permissions_denied">Without the storage permissions the app is unable to run perfectly. Are you sure you want to deny these permissions?</string>
    <string name="msg_basic_permissions">The application requires storage permissions to run perfectly. Can you allow storage permissions?</string>
    <string name="msg_qr_scan_permission_denied">Without this permission the app is unable to open camera and scan QR code. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_qr_scan_permission">To scan the QR code the application required access to the camera. Can you allow camera permission?</string>
    <string name="msg_calender_permission">To add event in calender the application require calender permission.Can you allow the permission? </string>
    <string name="msg_calender_permission_denied">Without this permission the app is unable to open calender. Are you sure you want to deny this permission?</string>

</resources>
